Tao Holland

Graphic Designer

9	316 Bruyere St, Ottawa, Canada K1N 0C3
	1 613 292 1712
\searrow	taoholland@gmail.com

https://www.behance.net/holl0208961e





OBJECTIVE

Seeking relevant professional work experience in Graphic Design.



EDUCATION

Algonquin College: 2015-Present

Graphic Design Diploma

Ottawa School of Art: 2014-2015

Fine Arts Portfolio Certificate

Acadia University: 2007-2009

Bachelor of Arts, Theatre Production



SKILLS AND PERSONAL ATTRIBUTES

-InDesign	
-Lightroom	-
-Photoshop	
-Illustrator	_
- After Effect	

- Experience Design
- Prop building and design
- Stage management
- Freelance painter
- •Freelance graphic designer
- Inventory management
- Customer service
- Point of sale
- ·Management and team leadership
- -WHIMIS

ABOUT ME

Experience working in fast paced environments. Possess demanding strong organizational, technical and interpersonal skills. Precise, trustworthy, and committed to superior customer service. Able to work well in a team environment as well as work independently. Creative fast thinking mind and able to multi task effectively. Artist, designer, traveler and scuba diver enthusiast.

WORK EXPERIENCE

RICHCRAFT HOMES

Graphic Design intern
June 2017-Present, Ottawa, Ontario

FREELANCE ARTIST

Jun 2015-Present, Ottawa, Ontario

UNIVERSITYHUB.CA

Freelance Graphic Designer
Apr 2016-Feb 2017, Ottawa, Ontario

FESTIVAL ANTIGONISH SUMMER THEATRE

Prop Builder/Designer and Stage Manager May 2015-Sept 2015, Antigonish, Nova Scotia

THE HUDSON BAY COMPANY

Sales Associate for Ladies Designer Fashion
Jun 2013-May 2015, Ottawa, Ontario

THE HUDSON BAY COMPANY

Sales Co-lead for Coach Designer Handbags Apr 2012-Dec 2012, Mississauga, Ontario

THE HUDSON BAY COMPANY

Sales Associate for Ladies Shoes and Handbags Sept 2011-Apr 2012, Mississauga, Ontario

AWARDS

HUDSON BAY CUSTOMER SERVICE EXCELLENCE AWARD.

SUMMER 2012, MISSISSAUGA ,ONTARIO